Thank you for watching
ME
Training for Instantaneous Force b 6th place
We are now holding a competition to train the only one of the children on the hill to survive in the age of variety.
Tonight, we're going to see who can do the best impersonation immediately after the topic is given in the extended imitation competition that was so much fun last week.
The challengers are as follows, including Nimura, who has been on a losing streak.
Mr. Himura, yes, you've been losing all week... I've been wanting to do it so bad I've been pushing it.
I've been pushing him so hard I can't help it... but he's completely outplayed me.
Yamashita, you're not motivated.
What's in it for me is to improve my speed, my speed, my speed... my future self.
Really?
I'm going to take the plunge.
I see.
Tiger, there's an actress from the morning dramas, so I think it'll broaden your range.
Will you play a gorilla?
If you play a gorilla in a gag or something in the future, if you're good with gorillas, the director will be like...
Ha-ha-ha!
Then it's all coming to you, isn't it?
Mr. Himura turned it down.
I can't give you a schedule.
Too busy.
Let's speed things up.
Okay.
Genre, this way.
A female comedian.
She's the one who's going to do it.
Here you go, sir.
It's not Schlick.
Oh, my God, what's that look?
What's wrong with your face?
What's that evil look on your face?
That's not my aunt's face, not after Schlick.
Why such a nasty face?
What's with that face?
What do you mean there's a handgun?
It's a handgun!
Yokorae's starting to look like an old man with missing teeth!
There's one more typical one.
Not a lot of horns!
Okay.
What the hell is that?
That's great!
Kubori, keep up the good work!
Okay, three to go.
Let's go... genre this way
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!
I'm the male comedian.
There he is, finally, a male comedian, this way, please.
Go ahead.
321, go ahead.
Janjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjanjan hidaka
I thought they were Fortix.
I thought they were Fortix, but they're round pebbles.
There we go.
What kind of mistake is that?
Yes, it's okay.
I'm sure you'll come up with something original.
Original, original, original.
Finally, the final battle between the third-term students.
Yamashita and Iwamoto.
Let's jump!
Wow!
Yamashita lost!
Iwamoto poses with guts!
This is for you!
Goat!
What's a goat?
321, please.
Ehhhh...
That's good.
That goat is not super good.
First goat in my life.
That goat is super good.
Wow!
You can do it, Kimura-san.
Dah!
You push.
Push it, and there's a female.
Dah!
Dah!Dah!
Nice.
You got a female collaboration when you pressed it.
First time and well done.
That's good.
I'm going to make it my speciality.
You lost to Yamashita.
I wanted to do it again.
Can you play the goat?
I can goat.
Please...
I'll eat it.
I knew I shouldn't have done it.
I said so myself.
I said I'd do it, I'll do it
Propolis.
Here you go.
Bon appétit!
Oh, it's hot!
It's hot!
They say it's stronger than ever!
The battle to determine the speed queen! From here on out, we're going to have a game tournament of instantaneous force!
The first one is up to you, Mr. Hinomura! The box contents quick move showdown!
The speed duel of "What's in the box? Four people will try to guess the correct answer at the same time, and those who can't guess the correct answer until the end will be asked to drink a penalty drink!
These four players will try their hand at a game that will test their quickness and courage!
Now, let's take the cloths all at once!
Three, two, one, open!
Give me other thanks. Give me other thanks.
Oh, man!
I don't know, I'm really scared.
I can't wait to do it!
I can't wait!
Kanagawa
I'm not scared.
Oh, as expected
The pine tree is
I'm scared
That's scary
How scary?
What's that smell?
That's not Propolis.
It smells like Propolis.
If you know what I'm talking about, press the button and come see me.
Let's guess what's in the box!
Let's do it!
Ah!
Oh, no!
Why not?
There it is!
It's the highest one.
Not now, not now!
What's this?
In a quiet voice.
She's crying... I can't understand her...
Correct!
Here we go!
Here it comes!
Here comes Matsuo!
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't.
He's going this fast?
Seriously, it's not that fast...
You're right.
One more to go!
One more to go.
There you go.
Oh, my God, you're touching it.
I know, I know, you should go like this more and more, like this, with both hands, both hands.
You can go all the way with both hands, and then...
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I know.
No, no, no, you better hold it, you better hold it, you better hold it, you better touch it more.
I don't know where they are.I don't know where they are.
Not that side, not that side.
Body more in front of you, in front of you.
Corner in front of you, corner in front of you.
Because the body is moving, it's moving.
Body lower right, lower right.
It's way, way, way up.
You know this?
I know it, I know it, I know it.
Up the wall, up the wall.
Ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh.
Right on top of the wall, there's a body coming in.
Oh, yes.
No, it's not.
Iwamoto, what are you doing?
Please touch it!
What are you doing?
Ew?
Aaaaah!
Oh no!
It's an ear!
Wait a minute, it came out!
What should I do?
I haven't seen it yet.
Let me in, please.
Why do I have to touch it?
It's coming out... it's coming out...
I'm sorry...
Why don't you touch it with the palm of your hand?
I was touching it with the back of my hand.
I'm around here somewhere
What's this?
I know what it is.
Wait, stranger!
Let's guess Kanagawa's, too.
Yamamoto's on the fence.
You'd better guess.
Oh, here he comes.
He's coming slowly.
That's right.
I see what you mean.
All right, everyone, go to your boxes.
Take a look... at your box.
I'm sorry... for touching you so much.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Yamamoto can handle it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sad.
I hated him.
I hate it.
If that's what this game usually is, it's the best reaction.
Yes, it is.
That's how it usually goes.
Iwamoto is the one who's wrong now.
What's wrong with you, touching Iwamoto's face?
What are you doing?
I didn't understand.
I've never touched a frog before.
I like them a lot.
I don't like them very much, but...
It's cute.
I think they're cute.
Did you see the frog?
The one I was touching.
You should see it.
Why don't you look at it?
She's here.
Oh, my God.
You're such a jerk.
I've been touching you.
Like this.
That's what I've been touching.
That's great.
That's great!
Kanagawha's the last one.
This time
That's why
Punishment drink for losing the game!
Here we go!Here we go.
He's crying and he's touching frogs.
Pro.
Okay, then.
Go ahead.
Go for it.
Better than going home.
Punishment game is over!
Let's continue with the speed game...
The first letter of the ancient alphabet is the first thing to be found in the studio in an instant and brought back to the studio.
The fastest one is the government, and the next three are Bartz, drinks, and the last one is the government.
Can you imagine what's in the studio?
Who's the strongest?
s gorilla is also good
I found out that he's surprisingly aggressive... and I thought he was going to do it so that Yukimoko wouldn't lose to her senpai.
If I win, I'm going to have to play Pros Pros Pros.
I'm sure you'll be fine, but games are fun because you're playing by the rules, and it doesn't matter if you can't get your senpai to drink or not.
I'm really determined to win, but on the other hand, yes, I'm serious about it, and I'll let the seniors drink.
I'm serious about it.
We don't know what we're going to get yet, so we don't know what we're going to get.
I don't know what's going to be in the game yet.
I don't know if it's still going on...
I'll tell him to do it.
Here's the first letter of the hunter's competition.
Me.
Me, me, me.
Me, me, me, me.
sand is over with bordikgas aaem
I'm so fast it's amazing hair ok so
I went over there and there was barley tea, and I thought, "I drank that earlier.
This is fast.
That's fast.
So the three of us are propolis.
That's great!
What's up?
I brought it.
What is it?
It starts with nothing.
If you're so lucky...
I'll be there.
I'll go.
Here you go.
I can't.
Then I would have preferred nothingness.
Nothing... nothing... nothing...
I learned a lot.
LOL.
Nice aggressiveness.
Aggressiveness is good. Two cups.
Laughs.
Nice aggressiveness.
And now, the three losers will be punished with a drink.
Here we go.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Yuck!
LOL!
I'm scared.
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it.
I get scared a lot.
Only Mugi-cha Mugi-cha.
I don't want to be here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Just you stay with me, Mr. Mugi-cha.
But it's just a tea kettle.
What's wrong?
It's propolis-flavored!
Propolis barley tea
I drank one, I'll take another
Sure.
But it's strong.
You're breathing.
He's breathing.
He's relieved.
I'm breathing.
Why are you breathing?Why are you breathing?
Nice. You're getting really good at making tea.
Yes, that's great. One more?
One more!
Oh, my God, it's like another shot of tequila.
It definitely tastes different now.
You can tell the change in the plum I've been drinking the most.
Oh my God, this is really not the variety.
What, no, no, no, no?
Oh, no!
Since it was decided so quickly, we'll have a second round with the same members.
Here are the letters of the theme.
Here we go!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
One more time! Again! I don't know what to do.
What, what, what, what?
Osamu!
Osamu! Osamu!
That's right!
Osamu OK!
Osamu! Osamu!
Osamu OK
How did you know my name was Osamu so quickly?
I've been thinking Osamu, Osamu
Sasarashi!
Great, you can call me Osamu-sansan from now on!
So, it's punishment drink time again for the three losers!
All right, let's start!
Start?
I misheard the call.
Oh, no!
That's good, that's good, that's good.
That's good. That's good.
What's up?
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
I don't see much!
What's wrong?
Uh-uh.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's a good second drink.
I'd rather hold my nose
I'm holding my nose
I'm like Mami Yamase
Ume already stopped
She'll be up and at 'em in no time
Oh, no.
Why do you want me to shake it?
All she says is, "Oh no!
Okay, we're going to have a face-saving final battle.
Let's continue... with Hiro, please. Margeon.
ME.
The game is to find the rain in the axe without using your hands. Four players try it at the same time, and the last one standing gets to drink the Burt's Drink, and wins.
You know, it tastes better with face powder all over it.
But if you get your face dirty, don't worry about selling your hair or anything, just get on with it.
If you show that you're willing to go the extra mile, then she'll get one, and that's good for the staff.
It's important to show that you're willing to go the extra mile... to win the final speed duel.
Now that we're all ready... the hair is so cute and pretty... and the moves are so cute... as usual...
I've never been to one before, but I'm sure it's my first time.
I've never been there before, but it's all about momentum, isn't it?
Yes, I'm going to make it dirty.
Yamashita, I want to win for sure! I want to win because nothing good has happened today.
Nothing good has happened today, so I definitely want to win.
It's my first time on TV with this visual, my first time with a pie in 7 years, my first time with this type of thing, my first time to make my face dirty.
It's my first time to make a mess.
I've never done a pie or anything like that before.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Embarrassed? Embarrassed? It's round. It's cute.
But I'm going to get it dirty.
I want her to win, so I'm not worried about her face anymore.
If we come in last... we'll have to play a penalty game.
The rain-eating contest!
Wait a minute. They're all at different distances.
Where are you coming from? From where you stand.
Careful, careful, careful.
Here we go. Great, great. It's so refreshing.
It's true. It's like a perm championship from the Showa era.
Like a model getting a perm.
Let's go! Get ready for the rain-eating contest!
Get ready.
Back up, back up, back up, back up, back up!Gone, gone, gone. Back, back, back.
There's rain, there's rain, there's rain. We'll just have to scrub it off with our faces.
It's pretty painful, so just keep your head up and keep breathing.
Just breathe. - Breathe. - Breathe? Is there rain?
Look for it, look for it, look for it, look for it, look for it, look for it.
Good luck. Now, there are three rain drops hidden in this powder.
I'll find them one by one.
Go, go, go! Press the fast button!
Show me Yamashita. Yamashita, front, front, front...
Don't drop it. Oh no...
Where should I add it?
Face the front, please. Face the front.
A little more to the right. Right, right, right!
Stop there. Let me see.
What do you think? Rain.
Okay.
We're through the bottom of the mountain. Next, clouds. Clouds.
Rain. Rain.
Okay...
Come on, Endo and Masayoshi, hang in there!
It's Endo and Masayoshi. Go, go, go!
Go, Endo! Go, Endo! Go, Masayoshi! Tell them to go for it!
Have you found them?
They're both looking for it... did you find Endo?
We haven't found him...
Masayoshi... have you found him yet?
Is there anything around there?
Don't make me laugh.
Don't make me laugh... but I'm focusing on that area.
There's something hard.
Check the inside of the nose...
Check the inside of the nose, the inside of the nose.
It's not in there, is it?
Hodgkiss, Masayoshi, it's always been in that corner.
It's not there anymore, is it?
Is there something in the middle?
There are three in this big box.
There are three?
Laughter
Why are Yamashita and Kubo going back?
Yamashita and Kubo have already cleared it.
Are we going to find a second one?
There isn't one...
Masayoshi and Endo found it quickly.
Masayoshi!
Nothing... nothing... nothing...
Kubo and Yamashita were fast!
Kubo and Yamashita are on their second search.
Why are you doing this?
I don't know.
It's fun.
They're having fun once they get started.
If you give them a purpose, they'll do their best.
That's right.
I can't find Endo and Masayoshi.
We'll have to do it long after everyone else is gone.
A one-on-one battle! Who will win in the end?
Powders elimination team's candy-eating contest!
Who will find Endo or Sugawara first?
Here they come! Endo's on us!
Come on, candy, face front!
Candy!
Yes!
-Yes!
Ha-ha-ha!
-That's it!
Did we lose? Shokichi.
No.
What?
What? What are you talking about?
Why does everyone want to go?
It's already over.
I'm trying to find something.
What? I'm pretty sure it's not here.
He said we could use our hands, too.
There it is.
Oh, I didn't know it was that easy.
There it is!
Hey, you know, you should learn how to find it with your face, for future reference.
Oh, I see.Yes, I see.
Remember this feeling.
I'll keep it in mind.
That was a good end.
Yes, it was a jaw bump.
Jaw bump?
Jaw bump.
It was a little bumpy.
I see.
If it's clean, it's like, it's fringed or something.
But, you know, it's a little bit like the hawk's nose when he was a kid.
Yes! Yes, yes, yes! Yes, yes, yes!
It's like the cheeks.
It's true.
It's cute, but...
Yamashita's number one.
Yay!
We did it!
Yamashita looks terrible.
Oh no...
Yamashita! Yamashita, are you fast?
Here you go. Is it me?
Mr. Yamashita, you're in trouble.
Oh, no.
You're like a relative.
Good morning. Long time no see.
What's this?
You're beautiful.
Beautiful, isn't it, Kubo?
Yes, it is
Good for you!
Kubo's nice, too. Cute.
Kubo's always white, so she won't change.
I won't change.
No change.
Then what's the point?
She didn't change at all.
I don't think he'll change.
Come on, Mr. Shoki.
Yes, sir.
Punishment then.
Who's this?
You complain a lot, don't you?
So, Sugawara will be punished.
Have you ever taken propolis?
It's my first time.
First time.
That's good. First time for many things.
Let's do it all at once.
Bon appétit.
Wow.
Oh, my gosh!
Boo hoo! A novel variety!
The girl in white paint... Wow!
I don't see a lot of great big brother here. Endo seigatsu!
Yoo-hoo!
We're not the only ones having this much fun, I wanted to give you a present...
Midsummer National Tour mobile selection process is now open!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe and like our channel.
See ya!